const data = {
  "trivias": [
    {
      "_id": "asdf1",
      "genre": "Addition",
      "questions": [
        { 
          "index": 0,
          "num": "Question 1",
          "problem": "1 + 1 = ?",
          "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
          "correctAnswer": "2",
        },
        {
          "index": 1,
          "num": "Question 2",
          "problem": "9 + 9 = ?",
          "answers": ["12", "18", "14", "15"],
          "correctAnswer": "18",
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "num": "Question 3",
          "problem": "89 + 34 = ?",
          "answers": ["153", "113", "143", "123"],
          "correctAnswer": "123",
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "num": "Question 4",
          "problem": "8 + 6 = ?",
          "answers": ["12", "13", "17", "14"],
          "correctAnswer": "14",
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "num": "Question 5",
          "problem": "36 + 54 = ?",
          "answers": ["82", "90", "104", "80"],
          "correctAnswer": "90",
        },
        {
          "index": 5,
          "num": "Question 6",
          "problem": "17 + 97 = ?",
          "answers": ["114", "124", "104", "95"],
          "correctAnswer": "114",
        },
        {
          "index": 6,
          "num": "Question 7",
          "problem": "27 + 38 = ?",
          "answers": ["62", "65", "74", "58"],
          "correctAnswer": "65",
        },
        {
          "index": 7,
          "num": "Question 8",
          "problem": "19 + 28 = ?",
          "answers": ["49", "36", "47", "51"],
          "correctAnswer": "47",
        },
        {
          "index": 8,
          "num": "Question 9",
          "problem": "8 + 1 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "6", "9", "10"],
          "correctAnswer": "9",
        },
        {
          "index": 9,
          "num": "Question 10",
          "problem": "6 + 7 = ?",
          "answers": ["15", "13", "24", "16"],
          "correctAnswer": "13",
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "_id": "asdf2",
      "genre": "Subtraction",
      "questions": [
        { 
          "index": 0,
          "num": "Question 1",
          "problem": "1 - 1 = ?",
          "answers": ["2", "1", "4", "0"],
          "correctAnswer": "0",
        },
        {
          "index": 1,
          "num": "Question 2",
          "problem": "9 - 5 = ?",
          "answers": ["6", "4", "3", "8"],
          "correctAnswer": "4",
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "num": "Question 3",
          "problem": "15 - 8 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "9", "5", "6"],
          "correctAnswer": "7",
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "num": "Question 4",
          "problem": "16 - 7 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "9", "5", "6"],
          "correctAnswer": "9",
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "num": "Question 5",
          "problem": "36 - 18 = ?",
          "answers": ["14", "18", "19", "16"],
          "correctAnswer": "18",
        },
        {
          "index": 5,
          "num": "Question 6",
          "problem": "78 - 27 = ?",
          "answers": ["19", "49", "51", "53"],
          "correctAnswer": "51",
        },
        {
          "index": 6,
          "num": "Question 7",
          "problem": "91 - 24 = ?",
          "answers": ["67", "65", "74", "49"],
          "correctAnswer": "67",
        },
        {
          "index": 7,
          "num": "Question 8",
          "problem": "56 - 23 = ?",
          "answers": ["29", "36", "33", "41"],
          "correctAnswer": "33",
        },
        {
          "index": 8,
          "num": "Question 9",
          "problem": "7 - 2 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "5", "9", "10"],
          "correctAnswer": "5",
        },
        {
          "index": 9,
          "num": "Question 10",
          "problem": "12 - 6 = ?",
          "answers": ["6", "13", "4", "9"],
          "correctAnswer": "6",
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "_id": "asdf3",
      "genre": "Multiplication",
      "questions": [
        { 
          "index": 0,
          "num": "Question 1",
          "problem": "1 x 1 = ?",
          "answers": ["2", "1", "0", "9"],
          "correctAnswer": "1",
        },
        {
          "index": 1,
          "num": "Question 2",
          "problem": "9 x 9 = ?",
          "answers": ["86", "81", "99", "15"],
          "correctAnswer": "81",
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "num": "Question 3",
          "problem": "8 x 6 = ?",
          "answers": ["48", "32", "23", "28"],
          "correctAnswer": "48",
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "num": "Question 4",
          "problem": "7 x 9 = ?",
          "answers": ["63", "13", "77", "69"],
          "correctAnswer": "63",
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "num": "Question 5",
          "problem": "11 x 12 = ?",
          "answers": ["82", "138", "102", "132"],
          "correctAnswer": "132",
        },
        {
          "index": 5,
          "num": "Question 6",
          "problem": "17 x 4 = ?",
          "answers": ["67", "68", "66", "95"],
          "correctAnswer": "68",
        },
        {
          "index": 6,
          "num": "Question 7",
          "problem": "5 x 7 = ?",
          "answers": ["66", "34", "35", "36"],
          "correctAnswer": "35",
        },
        {
          "index": 7,
          "num": "Question 8",
          "problem": "19 x 3 = ?",
          "answers": ["57", "36", "47", "51"],
          "correctAnswer": "57",
        },
        {
          "index": 8,
          "num": "Question 9",
          "problem": "80 x 0 = ?",
          "answers": ["0", "60", "80", "10"],
          "correctAnswer": "0",
        },
        {
          "index": 9,
          "num": "Question 10",
          "problem": "12 x 12 = ?",
          "answers": ["144", "134", "124", "116"],
          "correctAnswer": "144",
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "_id": "asdf3",
      "genre": "Division",
      "questions": [
        { 
          "index": 0,
          "num": "Question 1",
          "problem": "1 / 1 = ?",
          "answers": ["2", "3", "1", "5"],
          "correctAnswer": "1",
        },
        {
          "index": 1,
          "num": "Question 2",
          "problem": "10 / 2 = ?",
          "answers": ["2", "5", "4", "6"],
          "correctAnswer": "5",
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "num": "Question 3",
          "problem": "49 / 7 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "6", "8", "9"],
          "correctAnswer": "7",
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "num": "Question 4",
          "problem": "88 / 11 = ?",
          "answers": ["8", "7", "17", "11"],
          "correctAnswer": "8",
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "num": "Question 5",
          "problem": "36 / 9 = ?",
          "answers": ["4", "5", "6", "9"],
          "correctAnswer": "4",
        },
        {
          "index": 5,
          "num": "Question 6",
          "problem": "64 / 8 = ?",
          "answers": ["8", "9", "7", "6"],
          "correctAnswer": "8",
        },
        {
          "index": 6,
          "num": "Question 7",
          "problem": "108 / 12 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "8", "9", "5"],
          "correctAnswer": "9",
        },
        {
          "index": 7,
          "num": "Question 8",
          "problem": "27 / 9 = ?",
          "answers": ["3", "6", "4", "51"],
          "correctAnswer": "3",
        },
        {
          "index": 8,
          "num": "Question 9",
          "problem": "8 / 1 = ?",
          "answers": ["7", "6", "9", "8"],
          "correctAnswer": "8",
        },
        {
          "index": 9,
          "num": "Question 10",
          "problem": "72 / 9 = ?",
          "answers": ["8", "7", "6", "5"],
          "correctAnswer": "8",
        }
      ]
    },
  ]
}

export default data;